right some why well there we go pull a
corrective it's up a little bit
this is the beautiful yoga space that I
have access to all a lot of the time but
especially for the next month because
I'm hustling and I just came up here to
do some yoga give myself some time on
mother's day and they got come on I
didn't come on yesterday thank you on
the day before so I wanted to update
what people know what's going on and if
magic is happening the synchronicity of
life angel came on to my periscope and
introduced me to the world cafe which is
everything I've wanted to do online with
technology but in the real world and
reading the book the e-book right now
which is hard for me because I figured
that if something isn't exciting or it's
in really complex language by bringing
cattle I comprehended and so I can't
learn that way anymore I used to be able
to or if it is in simple enough language
and it is exciting
then I can't sit still over learn it and
so I'm like okay so read a piece get
excited go burn off the energy and we're
going to create we're going to views a
World Cafe in real life to create a
World Cafe online so that anyone
everywhere can come and have a
conversation that is meaningful and deep
as long as they have an internet
connection and a camera and a mic which
most people do did I know I realize
there's people in the world who do not
have those things and we can have
conversations on how to get them in
those days to include them in the
conversation we're gonna have the
conversation in real life but like how
conversations or meaning how
conversations are where all ideas come
from
and when the synchronicity of leg I keep
getting the same lesson but deeper and
deeper and deeper and taking the dog for
a walk this morning and it's like that
this cafe is basically one of the people
kind of wanted to do a year ago I was
like no they want to project well but it
was I had to get to this point she hurts
me okay and that I'm all about if we
don't have transparency and democracy
and we just release something into the
world that we then have to sell it to
them and I don't want to sell something
to someone I want it to be created
organically from within within the group
that's what I'm allowed to happen for me
right now is organic food for it to
emerge for me as an individual and as I
become the person I'm supposed to be to
birth the message the world happy
Mother's Day and allowing myself to
become that person give birth to me
you've birthed to the idea and the whole
thing is that if I do it myself and it's
all of who my ideas that I hold strongly
to them I then have to sell it to all of
you but if we can create the foundation
of like okay we want to create a
technology company even to transparent
and democratic and it starts with
conversations and powerful conversations
and having them online so that they're
accessible to the most people so let's
have a real world one where we can make
this atmosphere work ask the right
questions
which will be how do we make include
more people how do we include the
technology how do we create this online
so everyone can participate these that
is social media with the difference when
you can have a conversation a real
conversation around a virtual table
about what gender means to you how
climate change is impacting you how you
feel about poverty whether you're in
poverty or not and you can have because
from those conversations solutions
emerge and people want to take action on
them I would love to take action on my
edge
I'm not capable of doing it all on my
own but I like somehow to feel weirdly
capable of creating this world cafe
because I also talked about I asked
members of the keynotes after like four
people was again here before this like
World Cafe idea and was I guess I've
participated a few of them and that was
like the one person who was like I was
talking directly to I don't know if the
other ones even heard I think either
people or like a part of it so the
foundation or the richness of experience
and knowledge that I have surrounded
myself with is amazing I just have to
figure out how to tap in it's going to
be like hey can probably make this come
help me make the settings we can have
the conversation so the group
intelligence can emerge and we can
create something together that has never
before been done this fun world cafes
have absolutely none before and magic
has come out of them but the idea that
you get together and have a conversation
about how to include more people always
more people and always where they are
and when it doesn't work for us we
figure out why and create that
technology and that technology like
we're gonna have the conversations then
we're going to need those conversations
to become actually and although be
people who want to catalyze that action
or fizzle out will be like well why why
did it disallow to have the information
how do we have a place to hold the
information how do we get the right
people to the right projects how do we
follow through how do we need a project
management system how do we create this
World Cafe online now with minimal tech
like with what already exists or it can
be as little money as possible there is
a way to do these now everything's it's
gained technology with zoom with a
period with the ones that are there but
there are certain things that exist in a
royal cafe like calling people back to
the bigger group that would be Harvard
because what's the bigger group I don't
know that's why we're gonna have a
real-world ones monthly to brainstorm
before the Board of Directors can be
virtually online weekly to say okay
what's is what we're studying up from
hers the next
and make those we transparent available
to anyone who wants done with the beauty
of the group knowledge is it doesn't
have to be the same hundred let's have a
about hundred people every month that we
have a conversation but it doesn't have
to be the same hundred people especially
if we're and if that's if we get there
do 100 people together and they're like
one last ever no one came before it's
like how do we give you the information
for watching before how do we make that
available to you online in a way that's
understandable and usable so that we
don't need to keep having the same
people over and over again so if you
have your kids birthday party you don't
need to commit to coming into this it's
not a requirement this is an invitation
and the group comes up with the next
step and the group comes up so if you're
unable to make it you need to kind of
let that go that the group will come up
with amazingness that you're maybe not a
part of that discussion but you get to
still reap all this benefit of it I can
feel this all coming together it is so
close and I can figure out I'm figuring
out how to sit still for a moment not in
exhaustion but in with this energy
inside of me being able to like
dissipate it in a positive way and it's
happening I am so excited and now I'm
gonna go have a shower for Mother's Day
brunch so I'm not all sweating it before
for studying with my neighbors and and
then I'm gonna go have conversations
around the breakfast table that may or
may not organically be about the World
Cafe and I'm really good at so we could
instead and steer the conversation Oh
sidebar talk about what I want to talk
about and people are amazing at
accommodating it or not but it doesn't
meet their needs like let's change it
back to this topic okay so that is my
plan I keep finding on coming on here
and updating people and living my
mission even if this thing takes place
offline and it it's the only thing that
I'm still going to be sharing my story
because if it's beast even one person if
one person you find happiness through
the path that I have found happening
and I want to give that person happiness
so whatever happens I came on the social
media because I had to because that was
how I what I needed to do to make this
thing progress in the world now there's
a way to do without me be on social
media and I still want to be on social
media because I'm like no there's
something beautiful here there's
something that connects us that is a
conversation and although I don't
necessarily find conversation on YouTube
yet as like people aren't here yet and
they will come and we can have deep
meaningful conversations and then as I
make sense we move them towards our
world cafe app website saying that's
going to have real conversations that
everyday people have bypassing the
government bypassing the hierarchy and
just having a conversation with as many
of the stakeholders at the table as
possible whoever wants to be on that day
and we're organic action takes place and
we want to create projects we pray
apologetics and when we discover a
funding model I'm learning to let go of
mine virtually what this is supposed to
be as we have a discussion on a on a
sustainable funding model where we know
money is coming in and we don't have to
constantly be banking for it we then
have a pool of money to create these
amazing ideas we have to create World
Cafe so I was also sitting there being
like wait they try to take four brooms
and turn them into cafes you know what's
our name Cafe cafe and a lot of them are
cooking in the evening and when people
are available and getting those to be
those spaces and we can have them all
over the world in real life for people
who prefer to do this in real life
well discussing how to make this
available online and how to get all of
those conversations into like one
movement forward and we're gonna do it
this thing is so close take care happy
mother today whatever that means to you